propertyinvesting.com 2004-12-08

# Privacy Policy - PropertyInvesting.com

PropertyInvesting.com takes your privacy seriously, which is why we have created the following policy for your protection and security. Please read it carefully. 

####  What This Privacy Policy Covers 

This Privacy Policy ("The Policy") covers PropertyInvesting.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that PropertyInvesting.com collects when you are on the PropertyInvesting.com site, and when you use PropertyInvesting.com's services. 

The policy also covers PropertyInvesting.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that PropertyInvesting.com's business partners share with PropertyInvesting.com or that PropertyInvesting.com may collect on a partner's site. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that PropertyInvesting.com does not own or control, or to people that PropertyInvesting.com does not employ or manage. 

###  Information Collection and Use 

PropertyInvesting.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a PropertyInvesting.com newsletter or free report, submit feedback or sign on as a member of the PropertyInvesting.com community. PropertyInvesting.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 

When you register as a member of the PropertyInvesting.com community, we ask for your name, email address, and country of origin. Once you register with PropertyInvesting.com and sign in to our community, you are not anonymous to us. 

PropertyInvesting.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP Address, PropertyInvesting.com cookie information, and the page you requested. 

PropertyInvesting.com uses information for three general purposes: to customise the advertising and content you see on our pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

###  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

_PropertyInvesting.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone._

PropertyInvesting.com will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information; 

  * We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested; 

  * We need to send the information to companies that work on behalf of PropertyInvesting.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 

  * We respond to a compulsory court order to comply with due legal process; or 

  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the PropertyInvesting.com Rules \- or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

###  Cookies 

PropertyInvesting.com may set and access PropertyInvesting.com cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data - which often includes an anonymous unique identifier \- that is sent to your browser from a web site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

PropertyInvesting.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. The way other companies use their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to PropertyInvesting.com's cookies. 

PropertyInvesting.com uses web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with PropertyInvesting.com products and services. Web pages may contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel GIF" or "web beacon") that allow a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. 

###  Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences 

You may change or update the information you have supplied PropertyInvesting.com at any time. Please send an [e-mail](mailto:admin@propertyinvesting.com) with the update and we'll make the necessary changes as soon as possible. 

###  Security 

Every effort is made to keep your information private and away from hackers. However, it is not possible for us to guarantee your privacy. You should weigh up the risk that your details will be misused by hackers with the benefit of receiving the great information that this site has to offer. 

####  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

PropertyInvesting.com may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

####  Questions or Suggestions 

If you have questions or suggestions then please e-mail us at [admin@propertyinvesting.com](mailto:admin@propertyinvesting.com). 

This article reproduced from http://www.propertyinvesting.com/privacy.html with permission.  
© Copyright 2001-2004. PropertyInvesting.com Pty Ltd. All rights reserved.
